readbud.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy - readbud - Get paid to read and rate articles!

As per our Terms and Conditions, the privacy policy evaluates the measures we take to protect your privacy. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates unless the user wishes to store the cookie for auto-logging purposes which is at sole discretion of the user. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. In order to use our service as a member, cookies must be enabled. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

We partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

### Email Notifications

By registering as a member, you acknowledge our right to send relevant email notifications to your nominated registration email. These notifications can be disabled at any time by following the appropriate links for unsubscription in the emails originally received. 

### Security

We utilise and operate modern and robust security measures to protect the information you give to us from loss, misuse and alteration. We are constantly reviewing and upgrading these security measures to ensure the very best of protection to you.
